<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
<string name="L22HelpTitle">Level 22 - Mailbomber</string>
<string name="L22HelpPart1">Bei Mailbomber geht es um einen armen Bürohengst, der ständig mit Spammails zugemüllt wird. Viele dieser Emails zeigen ihm vielversprechende Wege, wie er schnell reich werden kann. Andere Mails hingegen befassen sich damit, wo sich unser Protagonist mit Viagra versorgen kann. Unser armer Held will sich nun ausreichend mit diesen Aufputschmitteln versorgen. Doch vorsicht, gewinnt er Geld, könnte er ja womöglich noch auf andere Gedanken kommen.</string>
<string name="L22HelpPart2">Therefore, the main goal of this game is, to ignore \'rich mails\', while at the same time paying attention to \'viagra mails\'. This works just like this :</string>
<string name="L22HelpPart3">Our protagonists sits in front of his computer screen, which in turn shows mails which constantly move towards him. This is also exactly the same, what you as a player are seeing. The mails have imprinted some terms in leet speak. You now have to type in those terms, before they reach slap into your face. But there is more to it : \'viagra\' have to be translated from leetspeak into english, while at the same time \'rich\' mails have to be typed in in leet speak, just like they are being displayed. Each success leads to the player loosing some money, as he successfully bought some viagra. On the other hand, he will win some money in case of a failure, as he clearly payed to much attention to those nifty \'rich\' mails (or didn\'t pay attention at all). Viagra mails are hinted by an orange color, while Rich mails are hinted by a blue mail color. </string>
<string name="L22HelpPart4">Die verwendeten Ressourcen werden recht simpel sein. Ein grüner Quad der den virtuellen Boden darstellen soll, definiert die Ränder der 3d Szene. Oberhalb dieses Quads bewegen sich simple Models von Emails auf den Spieler zu, und folgen dabei einem definierten Pfad von links nach rechts, sowie rechts nach links. Simple Soundeffekte sollen eingebaut werden, sowie eine entspannende Hintergrundmusik.</string>
<string name="L22nameofthegame">Mail Bomber</string>
</resources>
