<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
<string name="l12_title">Bye Bye, Bonuses!</string>
<string name="l12_paragraph01">All the financial institutes owned by our rich bunny have overcome the crisis and are rolling in cash once again. Of course this means huge bonuses for our bunny. The men carrying suitcases full of money are already on their way to bunny\'s home. Stop them to spare him even bigger wealth!</string>
<string name="l12_paragraph02">In this tower-defense-style level you have to arm bunny\'s front yard to blast those no good money carrying bastards back to where they came from. Spend as much money as possible on modern high-tech home security systems to stop your minions from reaching your doorstep. But beware: they are determined to hand you your hard earned bonuses and they are coming prepared.</string>
<string name="l12_paragraph03">The game is played from a bird\'s eye view. Enemies approach from the left side of the screen and try to reach the door on the right. The lawn in the middle can be equipped with various defense mechanisms that can be selected from the menu. All you have to do is place and maintain those devices, they handle the "rest". The game\'s goal is to stop as many money carriers as possible from reaching your house before the counter is running out.</string>

<string name="l12_tutorialtitle">Welcome to Bye Bye Boni!</string>
<string name="l12_intro">Our poor unlucky bunny, desperately trying to get rid of its heavy burden, also won a lottery. And now the money is delivered! Try to defend yourself from the delivering persons by the use of hired guns, which will shoot them with carrots, potatoes ...\n \n Availabe Mercenaries:\n</string>
<string name="l12_basic_tower">Basic cheap mercenary, only small damage and medium shooting rate.</string>
<string name="l12_advanced_tower">Better but more expensive ex-soldier. slow projectiles, but good damage and shooting rate. 5 projectiles per volley.</string>
<string name="l12_hyper_tower">Elite Mercenary fighting with massive power, medium damage bullets but high shooting rate and high bullet velocity. </string>
<string name="l12_freeze_tower">Specialized tower, freezes enemy to half speed. No damals, slow bullets.</string>
<string name="l12_finish">End of this level</string>
<string name="l12_enemies_fended">enemies fended off:</string>
<string name="l12_points">Money lost:</string>
</resources>
